(Leonard:)Okay. I'll confirm the travel arrangements
in the morning.
(Penny:)Okay, good.
- I do have to ask you one favor.
- Sure.
(Leonard:)Sheldon's nervous about me leaving,
keep an eye on him while I'm gone.
(Penny:)Oh, I don't know. Remember what happened
when I took care of your goldfish?
(Leonard:)Well, flush Sheldon down the toilet
and get me a new one.
(Leonard:)Really, you guys do not need
to throw me a going away party.
(Howard:)Are you kidding me?
How often can you say bon voyage...
(Howard:)...to somebody when they're
actually going on a voyage?
(Amy:)Hello, Rajesh.
(Howard(in Raj accent):)Hello, Amy. Nice to see you.
What can I say, it's funnier with the accent.
(Leonard:)There's beer in the fridge. Anyway, you guys
really don't need to make a big deal.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you're being selfish.
(Sheldon:)We need to give you a proper send-off
so we'll have closure...
(Sheldon:)...when you die at sea
and crabs eat your face.